写了一大堆东西在这玩意儿上
Writing all this stuff on this thing.
嗨 我是丹·哈萌  NBC《废柴联盟》的创剧人
Hi, I'm Dan Harmon, creator of NBC's Community.
真是个疯狂的第二季
What a crazy second season it's been.
演员们对他们的表演有何感受
How do the actors feel that they did?
他们如何看待彼此的表演
How do they feel each other did?
让我们在这一年一度的「演员评估」中找出答案
Let's find out in this annual round of Cast Evaluations.
感谢你们的参与
Thank you for coming in.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢你 老板
Thank you, creator.
真是疯狂的一季
It's been a crazy season.
这季真是疯狂又美好
It's been crazy and wonderful.
你觉得比第一季更好吗
You feel better than first season?
很明显 你看
Well, clearly, look.
感觉就像这部剧去年被砍了
It feels like we were canceled last year
然后我们闯入了旧的布景
and we broke into our old sets.
我觉得更好
I think better.
你是对的
I think you're right.
比第一季好
Better than the first.
因为我们加大了赌注
Cause we upped the ante.
是的
Yeah.
对吧
Right?
对
Yeah.
像是一切乾坤未定
We were like, all bets are off.
我们孤注一掷
We, we rolled the dice.
你好 丹
Hi, Dan.
我能吃点东西吗
Can I eat?
可以啊
Yeah.
我不想打断你
I don't want to interrupt your meal.
我会放下它
I'll put it down.
谢谢你的配合
Thank you for doing this.
让我擦个鼻涕先
Just let me just get my nose right.
头发
Hair.
咋了
Yeah.
你得弄回第一季的发型
We just got to go back to first season hair.
好的
Okay.
我在推特上备受打击
I've been taking a real beating on Twitter.
在推上 好吧
On the Twitter, okay.
在社交平台上
On social medias.
人们不喜欢你的直发
People do not like this straight hair.
行吧
Okay.
有人把图片发给我看
Somebody showed it to me straight.
我说 好吧 我不在乎
I said, fine, I don't care.
因为我们不关心这种事情
Cause we don't care about stuff like that.
我们并不肤浅
We're not superficial.
没错
Right.
我们可有内涵了
We're deep people.
确实
Oh, totally.
所以姐才是演员
That's why I'm an actress.
因为我对自己的外表没有意见
Cause I have no opinion about my appearance.
以我的口味 我个人认为要比第一季好
I personally think for my taste better than first season.
我觉得明显不同
I mean, definitely different.
电视剧真不该和观众叫板
It's not really a TV show's job to challenge people,
让他们感到不爽  颠覆他们的期望
make them uncomfortable, subvert their expectations.
不该这样
It's not.
我们的剧能这样搞 还挺酷的
It's kind of cool that we have a show that does that.
我们为本剧感到自豪
We're proud of the show.
我想说 是的
I mean like, yes.
如果我奶奶能对我说
It would be nice for my grandma to be like,
“我理解你今天所做的一切 ”那就太好了
I understood everything you did today.
如果她说“我看懂了这部剧”
Like when I saw the show, I got it.
“我完全看懂了”
I totally understood it.
那就太好了
Like that would be nice.
用电视节目来让你奶奶开心真是浪费
It is a waste of a TV show to make your grandma happy.
你完全可以给她喝一杯热可可饮料
When you could do that with a warm cup of cocoa.
我知道
I know.
只要是我和我奶奶聊天 问她
Just me talking to my grandma and being like,
觉得我的剧怎么样就够了
what'd you think of my show is enough.
是的 只要问一个关于抑郁症的问题就能让她开心
Yeah. Just asking a question about the depression will make her happy.
如果我们想要赚一大笔钱
If we wanted to make a bunch of money,
我们可以做个我对着镜头讲30分钟话的电视剧
we could have a TV show at 30 minutes of just me talking to the camera.
剧情只有“嘿伙计们 你们今天过得怎样?”
Just be like, hey guys, like, oh, how was your day?
“很好”
Good.
我们可以做一部这样的剧
Like we could do that.
这部剧现在完全可以卖给CBS
We literally could sell to CBS right now,
剧名为《你的孩子正在关心你》
a show called 'Your Kids Are Checking Up On You'
我现在浑身浴彩
I'm in paint right now,
我觉得这是一个不错的方式来结束这季
which I think is a good way to kind of finish the season off.
你头发上沾满了颜料 看起来有点原住民的感觉
You look vaguely aboriginal with crusted dye in your hair.
不好说 我甚至不知道自己是个啥样
I can't really, I don't even really know what I look like.
全凭感觉
I just feel it.
我感觉自己戴着头盔
I feel like I'm wearing a helmet,
即使我知道我头上什么都没戴
but I know I'm not wearing anything on my head.
你肯定是某个地方的土著
You're definitely indigenous to some area.
我也不好说
I don't know.
某地
A land.
我感觉自己是某地的先驱
I feel like I was the first one in some kind of land.
无论身处何方
Wherever we are.
我是你的先驱
I was your first.
我是这个办公室的开拓者
I was in this office first.
这是我的地盘
This was my land.
艾莉森·布里
Alison Brie.
喜欢她 好演员 演技棒 眼睛亮
Love her. Amazing actor, great range, beautiful eyes.
唐纳德·格洛弗
Donald Glover.
喜欢他 眼睛亮 身材棒
Love him. Amazing eyes, beautiful figure.
总之 演技棒
Just great range.
我觉得吉姆·拉什有点膨胀了
I think actually that Jim Rash is getting a little big for his britches.
是吗
Really?
他的压力越来越大  也越来越自大
And his britches are getting smaller and smaller as he gets bigger for them.
我不确定究竟是他遇到了烦心事还是他单纯自大
So I don't know if it's the britches problem or if it's Jim Rash,
但他真的有点嘴碎
but he really is getting a little mouthy.
有具体的例子吗
Any specific instances?
嗯 我们在排队买午餐
Well, we were in line for lunch
他觉得他应该站在我前面买炸薯条
and he decided he should be in front of me to get french fries.
这看起来不太对
Oh, so that doesn't seem right.
我会和他谈谈这件事的
I'm gonna talk to him about that.
别说是我说的
Please don't say my name.
不 我不会的
No, I won't.
伊薇特说你在排队买午饭时对她很粗鲁
Yvette says that you were very rude to her in the lunch line.
这是何时
When was this?
她没有具体说
She did not specify.
她就只说了我在排队买午饭时对她很粗鲁吗
She just said that Jim was very rude to me in the lunch line.
我问她是谁惹了麻烦
I asked her who's been a problem.
哇哦
Wow.
她立刻提到了你的名字
Your name came up instantly.
我知道
No, I know.
我知道她的意思
I know what she's talking about.
我们来个角色扮演吧
Can we do some role playing?
只是为了让我明白事情的原委
Just to take me through the situation as it happened?
嗯 那会很有帮助
Yeah, it'd be helpful.
哦呜 排队打午饭啦
Ooh, I'm in the lunch line.
好了
Okay.
哦呜
Ooh.
伊薇特 得赶快了 我们只有一个小时
Yvette, we're trying to, we only have an hour.
哦 吉姆
Oh, Jim.
哦 我知道你不会阻止我吃午餐的
Oh, I know you're not going to stop me from getting my lunch.
伊薇特 你不必在休息时间还抓着你的手提包
Okay, Yvette, you don't have to hold onto the purse while we're on break.
你能帮我拿些薯条吗
Would you please help me get those french fries
从那边的盘子里
off of that plate over there?
我知道你会帮我拿薯条的
I know you're going to help me get those french fries.
是的 我会
Yeah, okay.
好吧 伊薇特 我会去拿
Yes, Yvette, I will.
听起来好像是她的错
It sounds like the fault lies with her.
确实是
It really does.
所以接下来是我想做的
So here's what I'd like to do.
我想让你在第三季中出演她的角色
I'd like to give you her part in a third season.
那可真是谢谢你了
Oh, thank you.
现在不是让你演特洛伊了
Now, it's not Donald, but it's-
不 不 没关系
No, no, it's okay.
那就来演一段吧
Well, let's do the scene.
我可能会想要带点口音什么的  换个方式来演她
I will want to maybe play with an accent or something, sort of take her a different way.
你想试试吗
Would you want to take it for a spin?
是的 让我们看看伊薇特会变成啥样
Yeah, let's just see what Yvette would sound like.
在他娶了别人之后
And after he marries someone else,
如果你还和他上床
if you jump into the sack with him,
你真是个天使  只要你不用套套
you're an angel, so long as you don't use protection.
我很高兴你说出了心里话
I'm so glad you're enjoying this.
我希望那个偷笔贼好好享受
And I hope whoever stole that pen enjoys it.
在地狱里
In Hell.
就像我说的 用颠覆的方式来演
So like I said, just a different way to go with it.
你主持了第一季的《周六夜现场》
You were on SNL for the first season
然后你就去拍电影了
and then you moved on to your movie career.
这是我待过的最长的项目
This is the longest I've been on anything.
这是最长寿的电视节目
This is the longest TV show.
是的
Yeah.
好吧 我还在福克斯台待了五周
Well, I had that five week stint at Fox.
我笑是因为 我想到了
I'm laughing because I'm recalling
你在那个节目上最搞笑的段子
one of the funny bits you did on that show.
乔尔很好
Joel's great.
乔尔没啥问题
Joel's not a problem.
你不担心他的...
You're not worried about his...
他不吃东西
not eating.
是的 他不吃 他是这样的
Oh no, he doesn't eat, no.
所有人都知道 但没人关心
Everyone acknowledges this, but nobody's concerned.
他很高兴自己能减肥
No, he's so happy with his weight loss.
好吧 厌食症患者也这么说
Okay, well that's what anorexics say too.
那些家伙都有点饮食失调  我不骗你
Yeah, there's a bit of an eating disorder going on with those guys, I won't lie to you.
我知道你不在场 你在奥林匹斯山
I know you're not there, you're on Mount Olympus,
你在施展你的魔法
you know, working your magic.
我看到了他们的暴饮暴食 有点...
And I see the binging and purging that's going on and it's kind of.
所他们在大吃大喝 是吗
So they're binging and purging,
这不是厌食症 而是暴食症
it's not anorexia, it's bulimia.
我认为这是暴食症的特点
I think it's bulimic in nature.
这些家伙有很多暴食的行为
There's a lot of bulimic acting going on
没有女生 都是男生在吃
from none of the girls, just all guys.
那我要和他们谈谈吗
So do I talk to them?
我不知道
I don't know.
这事儿该我管吗
Is that my responsibility?
我找他们谈过了 作为一名前医生
I tried, look, being a former doctor,
我尝试告诫他们 但被无视了
I try talking to them and they ignore me
他们还说我胖 叫我肥仔
and they call me fat, fatty.
你担心唐纳德和乔尔吗
Do you worry about Donald and Joel?
他们锻炼得很多 吃得很少
They're working out a lot and they're eating very little.
他们根本不吃 他们只做俯卧撑
They don't eat at all, they just do push-ups.
不夸张地说 这就是他们现在的动力来源
Literally that's their, that's the engine they're running on right now.
他们不吃东西  光做俯卧撑
They're just doing push-ups and not eating.
这件事有我的责任吗
Like, what is my responsibility there?
大了去了
I think it's big.
我觉得你得对这件事负很大的责任
I think you have a large responsibility with this one.
我试着和乔尔谈话
I tried bringing it up with Joel
然后我一不小心就开始表扬他了
and I accidentally just started complimenting him
我把事情弄得更糟了
so I made it worse.
我感觉很明显的是
I feel that it's obvious...
你在身体上
that you physically have...
对自己照顾得
been taking care of yourself
更加积极了 在本季
more aggressively this season.
西克莱斯特: 《美国偶像》主持人 试播集Troy初遇Jeff时对他的称呼
乔尔在他主持的节目《杂烩汤》中经常拿西克雷斯特的身高开玩笑
哇 吃吧 西克莱斯特
Wow. Eat that. Seacrest.
如果要你扮演剧中的其他角色
If you were gonna be any other character on the show,
你会选谁
who would it be?
我觉得皮尔斯很好玩
I think Pierce would be fun.
我觉得演皮尔斯会很好玩
I think Pierce would be a fun character to play.
快来双人跳
Double bounce me.
你为啥要这样
Why are you doing this?
皮尔斯 够了
Pierce, that's enough.
我恨你
I hate you.
快给老子跳
Double bounce me.
天父
Father?
我会把这个说法抛给你
I would like to, I'll throw this statement at you.
你告诉我是真是假
You tell me true or false.
今年 我完全捕捉到了黑人女性的经历
I fully and completely captured the black woman experience
从你的角色身上
with your character this year.
看起来某人的生活
Looks like someone narrowly avoided
过得十分不浪荡
a "lifestyle mistake" of their own.
难道勾搭光棍才叫浪荡吗
Or is it only bad if you sleep with unmarried men?
圣经可不承认离婚  布雷塔
The Bible doesn't recognize divorce, Brita.
一旦结婚  他就永远是你的丈夫
Oh no, when you marry a man, he's your, he's your man.
在你看来
Well, if in your opinion,
你想在第三季做点啥
what would you like to do in the third season?
我想和某人演更多对手戏
Well, I would love to have more scenes with,
我从未和唐纳德对过戏
I've never worked with Donald Glover.
我和唐纳德从来没一起拍过单独的对手戏
Me and Troy have never had a scene with just the two of us.
那会很好玩
That would be fun.
我想再和乔尔有点互动
I'd love to have something else with Joel.
这季我和乔尔也没拍过单独的对手戏
I never worked with Joel this season, just me and him.
我也怀念和女生们一起玩
I missed playing with the girls more.
上一季  你知道的  我经常
Like last year, I got to do a lot of, you know,
与艾莉森和吉莉安一起玩耍
capers with Annie and Gillian.
如果你不搭配乔尔
What did it, if you didn't work with Joel,
不和唐纳德一起
you didn't work with Donald,
也不和女生们玩  你还能演啥
and you didn't work with the girls, what did you do?
我还有更多的戏份吗
Like to have more to do?
我认为我们能做的最好的事情就是我们正在做的事情
I think the best thing we can do is just what we're doing.
搞笑
Be funny.
越搞笑越好
The funnier, the better.
我一直想做的就是让人们开怀大笑
That's all I've ever really wanted to do is make people laugh.
不是那种在学校里的小丑什么的
Not like a clown in school or something,
而是
but just,
这是件很轻松的事
it's so relaxing.
就像打喷嚏一样
It's just like a sneeze.
好吧  这是个非常严肃的采访
Well, this has been a very serious interview.
但是我不想太严肃
Well, I didn't want it to be that way.
不 但我
No, but I,
如果你不介意 我想给你看看我的迪克
If you don't mind, I'd like to show you my dick.
真不错
It's amazing.
是的 我知道
Yeah, I know.
现在  地板上有点脏了
Right now, it's getting a little dirty on the floor, but.
我对它一直都露在外面感到震惊
I'm shocked that it was out the whole time.
很多人都以为它...
Well, a lot of people think it's, you know,
是管道之类的东西
just piping or something.
再见
So long.
非常感谢你们
Thank you very much.
哇哦
Wow.
真是发人深省又鼓舞人心
Well, that was edifying and emboldening.
我们记住了什么
What did we learn?
来回顾一下
Let's recap.
现在让我们进入正题
Now let's get down to brass tacks.
在屏幕下方
Along the bottom of your screen,
你会看到《废柴联盟》第二季中出现的常规角色
you should see an array of the regular characters featured in season two of Community.
如果你有一台索尼电视
If you have a Sony television,
你可以伸手触摸选择角色
you have the ability to reach out and touch the face of the character
不让TA在第三季回归
you'd like not to return for season 3.
请慎重选择
Please choose carefully.
你只能...
You'll only be able to...
好的 那就切维吧
Okay, Chevy Chase then.
完事了
All right.
真是个果断的决定
Well, that was a remarkably quick decision.
开了眼了
I've never seen anything like that.
听着  咱们秋季再见
Look, we'll see you in the fall
如果NBC还没炒了我的话
if NBC gets back to me.
晚安
Good night.
还得填完这些表格
Filling out these forms.
填表下班
Filling them out.